linkdir4u.com 2010-03-23

# Linkdir4u.com - Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

(last update: Mar 2010)

**Information we gather**

The following information is gathered from our website visitors:  
name, email address and website informations.

**How we use the information we gather**

We use the information to enhance your visitor experience. To safeguard your personal information, we do not sell or share it.

**The people that are given access to this information**

Your personal information is accessible by site administrator and website editors.

**Our use of cookies**

Our website makes use of cookies which are small digital files that are stored in your web browser that enable us to track your return visits to our website.

Your browser settings may allow you to block these cookies, but we recommend you have them enabled to help us personalise your experience of our website.

Additionally, 3rd party advertisers on our site may use cookies for tracking purposes. linkdir4u.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to visitors based on their visit to sites they visit on the Internet.

Website visitors may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
